const quiz3data = [
    {
      question: "James recommend ___ holidays in Corfu.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "going", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "to go", isCorrect: false},
     ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: stop, finish, imagine, suggest, recommend, avoid, mind, miss, risk, enjoy. '
   },
    {
      question: "I fancy ___ in nice restaurants with good friends.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to eat", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "eating", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Verbs of liking and disliking such as: enjoy, hate, fancy, like, love etc are followed by the -ing form.'
   },
    {
      question: "When you leave the hotel, please leave your key ___ reception?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "at", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "in", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: offer, manage, arrange, decide, deserve, learn, tend, promise etc.'
   },
    {
      question: "I recommend _____ by plane.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to travel", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "travelling", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: stop, finish, imagine, suggest, recommend, avoid, mind, miss, risk, enjoy.'
   },
    {
      question: "Henry learned ___ French.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to speak", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "speaking", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: choose, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
   },
    {
      question: "we chose ___ by bus because it was cheaper than train.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to travel", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "travelling", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: choose, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
   },
    {
      question: "I have just finished ___ my room.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to clean", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "cleaning", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: imagine, avoid, consider, finish, stop, risk etc.'
   },
    {
      question: "I agree ___ you my new bicycle. ",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to lend", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "lending", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: agree, choose, decide, plan, forget, expect etc'
   },
    {
      question: "Paul regretted ___ these bad things to me.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "saying", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "to say", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: regret, recommend, admit, avoid, imagine, finish, consider, deny, risk, fancy etc'
    },
    {
      question: "Sally hopes ___ London one day.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "visiting", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "to visit", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: hope, decide, expect, forget, intend, learn, prefer, plan, remember, want etc.'
    },
      {
        question: "He considered ___ a new car.",
        answersList: [
          {answer: "to buy", isCorrect: false},
          {answer: "buying", isCorrect: true},
        ],
        help: 'Some verbs that are followed by -ing: stop, recommend, admit, avoid, imagine, finish, consider, deny, risk, fancy etc'
    },
      {
        question: "John refused ____ this silly costume.",
        answersList: [
          {answer: "wearing", isCorrect: false},
          {answer: "to wear", isCorrect: true},
        ],
        help: 'Some verbs that are followed by to + infinitive: refuse, decide, expect, forget, hope, intend, learn, prefer, plan, want etc.'
    },
  ]
export default quiz3data
